test. Okay. Thank you. Good evening
everyone. Now call to order this uh May
5th, 2025 meeting of committees of
council. We'll begin with the roll call
of members. Mr. Harris. Yes, Madam
President. Mr. M here. Mr. Roya here.
Mr. Cle here. Miss Craig here. Miss Diaz
here. Mr. Hirs here. President B here. A
few reminders at the top of the meeting.
Uh first for any members of council, the
public or the administration that will
speaking that will be speaking this
evening, please do so directly into the
microphone so we can be heard on our
temporary system. Uh if you haven't
already, please silence your phones and
devices. This meeting and its
participants are being recorded. Tonight
we have meetings of committees of
council. There are no general public
comment periods during these meetings.
However, committee chairs will call for
comments from the public on legislative
items. Comments are limited to three
minutes per speaker and must begin with
your name and block of residence for the
meeting
record. Uh we'll now go uh move to the
approval of the minutes of the April
1st, 2025 committee meeting.
Motion to approve. Second. We have a
motion and a second. Counselors, any
comments on the meeting minutes?
Hearing none. Mr. Harris. Mr. Madd. I.
Mr. Roya. I. Mr. Please. I. Miss. Craig.
I. Miss Diaz.
Mr. Hersh. I. President Baker.
I. Great. We will then go to the finance
committee. Councelor Royo. Thank you,
Council President. Uh, we have one item
on our agenda this evening. Resolution
number 37 uh authorizing the donation of
339 through 341 Beaver Street to Saka
Development. Um and I don't see director
Campbell here but I'm not sure gonna be
me. Oh, Mayor Sarra. Uh thank you um
councelor Royo. I
um will just pro provide a a brief
background. We we had reported some of
this to council I believe at the end of
2023.
Um if you recall this this particular
parcel located on Beaver Street has had
a long history um beginning with um uh
Lancaster Equity and uh the community
action partnership. It was then
transferred to uh Rackle. Um and we were
moving forward uh with park planning
that was um contemplated uh when it was
owned by the previously by Lancaster
Equity. Before that, it had um been
contemplated to be a community garden.
By the end of 2023,
uh you may recall we had we had run into
some sever some significant roadblocks
related to the development of this
parcel uh for a park. One was that we
could not secure um a an an exit onto
Queen Street um because of the property
ownership along Queen Street. So it was
one way in and one way out of the park.
Um we were uh attempting to to um
address some of the safety concerns
through some subdivision and uh we had
two uh adjacent property owners that
were were interested in that
subdivision, but then one uh withdrew
and then subsequently the cost ballooned
and so the cost per square footage went
um pretty high. So originally we
estimated $250,000 and cost estimates
were running more towards
$600,000. So for all of these reasons um
the uh city opted to uh hit pause on
developing this into a park and uh began
to contemplate uh some other
opportunities uh to align with the
priorities of the city primarily related
to housing which brings us to today.
Um the property in April 2023 was
transitioned back to the city from
Rackle. This was a decision that was
made um in um as I mentioned in April at
a redevelopment authority meeting that
brought it back to us and then is now
coming to you. And this is a uh
resolution that would transition the
ownership of this property to uh SAKA
for the development of uh affordable
housing as indicated in the uh
resolution. There are deed restrictions
um that uh provide affordability
criteria and terms related to that
affordability criteria which are
consistent with uh other affordable
housing investments that the city has
made. Um Saka believes that they can
develop this property into potentially
five units. They are doing a lot of work
on Beaver Street already and
historically. Um they are currently
constructing um a new units at the
corner of Beaver and I believe it's
Andrew Street and they are renovating
another property that was uh damaged by
fire um in the next I think it's the 400
block or 500 block um 500 block and then
uh they had also done some re uh
renovation of other properties on the
300 block. So they have a history of
working in the neighborhood. Um again
this is a donation of property to the uh
to Saka for the express purpose of
affordable housing.
Thank you. Mayor Sarra um just one
question. Would you be able to elaborate
a little bit more on the income criteria
for that will be listed in the deed
restriction? Uh yes it's in the
resolution.
So give me a moment to pull that up. My
apologies if that was listed
there. Council Royo, I do have it in
front of me. Okay. Yes. Thank you.
Sorry. It's um in under section one. Um,
it's to be
um an occupier whose annual family
income is at or below 80% of the
Lancaster County area median income at
the time of sale or rented to a tenant
whose annual family income is at or
below 60% of the Lancaster County area
median income and that restrictions in
place for 15 years. Thank you, Council
President.
Any questions or comments from the
finance committee?
full council. Council, council
president, council, thank you. Um, to be
clear, uh, when looking at this parcel,
there is this is an empty lot and maybe
some garages. Is that correct, Mayor
Saji? Only only the empty lot. The
garages are not owned. Uh, they're
privately owned. Got it. So, this is an
empty lot that has nothing on it.
Correct. Okay. Thank
you.
Any additional questions or comments?
Council Med. Uh thank you, councelor
Royo. Uh my question goes towards some
of the deed restrictions. Um and uh just
to be clear, this is in perpetuity for
ever. Um and there
is along with the land is the agreement
that it's going to stay in this use is
just my question.
the the affordability restriction is in
full force in effect for a period of 15
years from the date of the conveyance of
this property to SAKA the restriction
period and that SAKa by accepting
delivery of the deed covenants on behalf
of SAKA its successors and assigns to
perform and abide by said terms
conditions and provisions. Uh so it it
is a 15-year restriction. These are the
same um uh uh restrictions that are used
through uh the redevelopment authority
and I believe other uh affordable
housing projects and I'm looking to the
housing team here uh who are shaking
their heads. Yes.
Uh thank you. And then also just my
final question given that this is on a
residential block um will we will Saka
also commit to making the roads are um
the way that they were found when the
development is done and what will the
impact of the development have on the
neighbors on the block. Um so with with
any construction there are uh definitely
impacts uh to the to the surrounding
residents and uh Saka has as I mentioned
um been doing projects uh on these few
blocks three, four and 500 of Beaver
Street. I I'm not I I'm not anticipating
that there is going to be need for a lot
of work in the streets. Uh there may be
sidewalk related work that needs to get
done, but that would that all of this
has to go through our um uh you know our
building codes, all of that process has
to happen. And so this is just the
conveyance of the property to Saka at
this point.
Thank you. And and the only reason I
mentioned that is because it's kind of a
skinny street on that block. Uh but it
is a skinny street. So uh but that uh
unless director that concludes my
questions council. Thank you council.
Very briefly councelor Ahmed. Thank you.
It's a good question. I I just wanted to
note as part of any land development
project um that is part of the
consideration. What what typically
happens is the city will take um a an
amount of money in escrow to protect any
of the uh public assets. So, if a
sidewalk is uh torn up, if a street is
removed, uh if there's a utility uh line
that needs to be put in, uh that's
required to be repaired uh by the
developer. Thank you. And um one last
question, I guess, is um regarding the
15-year restrictions um when year 16
comes, does that mean that I mean I know
that Saka most likely wouldn't sell it
to like the highest bidder, but what
happens to the land agreement at year
16? Yeah, typically uh in these cases
and and SAK's uh used this model in some
of their other homes uh the idea is that
that uh restriction is in place for 15
years. They have primarily specialized
in owner occupied units and the idea is
that the owner of that uh of that home
is able to build wealth and equity uh in
that home uh and then uh hopefully keep
it in the family if they so wish or if
they are to resell it then to capitalize
on that equity. Um so at that time they
would be able to sell it to um
uh any other buyer. The restriction does
cease after that 15-year period.
Um I I think this is contemplated as
possibly owner occupied or rental units.
If I um read the resolution uh
correctly, in the case of the uh rental
unit, that would that would again remain
in place for uh the 15 15 years. I will
say with most uh nonprofit uh partners
that we have like SAKA who are focused
on affordable housing, there is an
opportunity to essentially re re-up and
then uh dedicate that uh unit again for
um affordable housing for another
15-year period, for example. um that
that would require possibly um other
subsidy or refinancing at that point.
But that would be the decision of the of
Saka in this case and would it be the
city's decision to reup the 15 years? Uh
that's correct. It would be Saka's
choice at that point. Thank you. And
that concludes my questions. Thank you.
Thank you, Director Delves. Any
additional questions or comments from
council from the public?
Well, with that, I'll motion to move
resolution number.
You have a comment, Miss Gomez? Yes, I
have a
comment regards to Excuse me.
Susie Gomez, 115 North
Reservoir. Okay. So, um I just had a
comment. Um I firmly believe that if the
city is considering transferring two
properties to Saka, an organization that
sells homes at market price for profit,
we should instead prioritize preparation
for the polite and Dixon families. Um,
mayor stated that the city can simply
give away the fire station 6 property,
which raises questions about fairness
and community benefit rather than
allowing a profit driven uh transaction.
We should honor the legacy of Nelson
Polite senior, a reverend leader or of
the civil rights movement after whom the
city hall is named and his father
Abraham Polite whose parents were
enslaved in Ridgeland, Norh South
Carolina. This deep uh historic
historical connection underscores the
need of restorative justice.
Additionally, we should support Reverend
Kevin Polite's vision for community
upliftment as he emphasized uh last
Tuesday, focusing on providing resources
for our community's children and
supporting the less fortunate. By
redirecting these properties to
initiatives led by the Polite family, we
can invest in SOE future, fostering
equity and opportunity while paying
tribute to their enduring contribution
to our city's um history and values. And
I do know that SAKa is receiving this um
as a a grant. So I'm not saying it's for
profit. I'm just speculating that there
are other things that we could also
implement. Thank you. Thank you, Miss
Gomez. Any additional questions from the
public?
Uh, with that, I will motion to move
resolution number 37 to the next full
council meeting.
Just need a second.
Uh, all those in favor? I thank you. Uh,
council president, that concludes the
finance committee. Thank you very much,
councelor
Royal. We'll now move to our public
works committee. Councelor Hirs.
Thank you, Council President. We have uh
one agenda uh one item on our agenda
tonight. Um a resolution recognizing
National Public Works Week, which is
coming up from uh May 18th to May 24th.
Um, I'd like to invite uh, Director
Campbell up to say a few more words
about this resolution.
Thank you all. We're we're very proud of
being able to celebrate uh or nominate
the celebration of National Public Works
Week. Um this year the National Public
Works Week motto is people, purpose, and
presence. We we believe that what we are
trying to do and continue to do is be as
present as possible where we can in the
public right of way during vision zero
in the um water and wastewater realm as
well as the storm water realm capital
construction and operations and
sustainability in the environment.
Last year, the the National Public Works
model was dedicated to public property
uh dedicated to the quality of life,
which is exactly what our model was as
adopted in 2020. Um we're very very
proud of that. If you wish, and I I did
not have the foresight to put it up to
have it launched for today, but if you
go to the website, the the city of
Lancaster website, the DPW website,
there is There is at least one and I
believe up to five public service
announcements, videos that talk a little
bit more about what we do, how we do it,
uh where we're interviewing people,
staff in the public right in the public
right of way and in the in public works
and they speak to what they do and why
they're proud of the work that they do.
We're very much in favor of this uh
resolution and we're hoping that uh not
only is it recognized uh as you see all
of our people in our bright yellow vests
throughout the month of May, throughout
mayor's neighborhood month, but also
there's going to be a a Did you mention
the baseball game? I did not. It's going
to the uh we have we have arranged for
the for the staff of DPW for a baseball
game uh at at Clipper Stadium on Sunday
the 18th u that benefits the staff of of
DPW and um we're very much looking
forward to other opportunities for our
staff to be recognized.
Thank you very much, Director Campbell.
Yeah. Um that's a really nice uh gesture
to to the public works employees and
their families. Um all I'll add is that
um you know public works are are things
that I think a lot of us uh take for
granted. Um you know we take for granted
that when we turn the water on the water
comes out of the tap and that we flush
our toilet it goes somewhere and that
you know our trash goes somewhere. Um
that storm water is managed. um all
these things that we only tend to notice
them when it's not working. Um we don't
necessarily appreciate the most of the
time when it is working and all of the
all of the hard work that goes into the
behind the scenes of that and that's um
the hundreds of uh public works
employees that work every day to make
that happen. Um so I'm really glad that
we are uh doing this resolution and
we'll have more to say on the 13th.
Um, with that I will make a motion to
move this to our full meeting of council
on uh Tuesday, May 13th. Second. All
those in favor? I
I'm sorry. I just realized I did not ask
for comment from council or committee.
Any comment?
I'll just echo your thanks to the
Department of Public Works uh and to
Director Campbell for his leadership in
that department. Um, I may have more to
say on the 13th, but we're excited to
honor your staff again this year. Thank
you.
And with that, that will conclude the
public works committee. Thank you very
much. Our next committee, community
planning council Craig. Thank you,
Council
President. We have two items on the
agenda this
evening. Is it
Is that better? Yeah.
Okay. Um, we have two items on the
agenda this evening. First being
resolution number
36, 2025 amending the official sewers
facility plan to include AM Global
Holdings project at 617 Fremont Street.
Bring that down real close to your
Yeah. Is it on or off? Is it turned on?
Okay. Better. Perfect. All right. Lauren
Finn, senior planner. Um, this is a
pretty simple sewer planning module.
um it actually went through you all and
was approved um already, but I jumped
the gun and so when they um got it up at
the state level, we had approved it
before the county. So, it's just coming
back at you now that the county has
approved it. So, the plan looks good and
just a step in the process.
Thank you so much. Yes, we've done these
several time times before and um I
understand that it's a a new land
development that meets all the criteria
to
Yes. forward. Yep. So with that, I would
ask, are there any questions from the
committee?
Any questions from the public?
Jose River 100 block of coal.
My question is, are we getting a new
water station, you know, because that
whole thing is like from the 1800s for
that particular
Well, yes. All the tainted water and
everything.
But you're not fixing the main project,
the whole
That's the problem.
Thank
you. Um, with that, I will um make a
motion to move this to full council
on
think is it the 27th? Yes. Would it
would it be amendable to uh move this to
the 27th uh or the 13th?
It doesn't really make a difference.
Okay. Yeah.
I'll make a motion to move this to full
counsel on the 27th.
Second. All those in favor? I. Thank
you. Thank you.
Our second item on the agenda this
evening is administration bill number
four amending the historic district
ordinance. And I see Mr. Del making his
way to the
podium. Good evening.
Good evening
again.
Um, yes. Uh, thank you. Um, just wanted
to give you a little more uh context
about the proposed uh minor amendments
to uh chapter 155 of the city code. Uh,
this relates to the historic districts
ordinance. Um, essentially the
administration has proposed an update to
the definition of building official
within the historic district's
ordinance.
Um, one of the things that we're uh
trying to create here is more
flexibility uh for appointments to the
historic architectural review board and
to the historical commission. Um, if you
look uh at the code uh within chapter
155, it refers to the building official,
meaning uh one I presume that that dates
back to when the city only had uh one
building official. At this time, now we
have a set of professional staff within
uh the building codes bureau that um is
responsible for these duties. Um Mr.
John Lefever has been serving on the
board uh both and historical commission
for some time. Uh we would like more
flexibility in the definition uh to
allow other certified staff within the
bureau to to serve on those boards. Uh
it also gave us an opportunity to update
that definition so that it was in line
with um the Department of Labor
standards for building code
certifications. So if uh if we look at
the bear with me for a sec a moment
here got my papers out of
order. As you'll see in the new
definition, uh, it states, "A building
official is a building inspector
certified as such by the Pennsylvania
Department of Labor and Industry who is
either an employee of the city, an
independent contractor of the city or
otherwise retained by the city and who
their certification by the Pennsylvania
Department of Labor and Industry and
with authorization from the director of
community planning and economic
development is authorized to issue
permits for construction, alteration,
repair, or demolition, etc." and it goes
on from there. Um, one other element to
this change in the code is it
uh well I should back up and say uh
since since the beginning of this
ordinance uh it was always contemplated
that a building official served on HARB
or the historical commission uh that we
want that professional designation to
remain. Uh the only difference is we've
also proposed in this ordinance that um
city council is delegating that
designation of the building code
official to the director of community
planning and economic development. So
essentially that would give uh a person
in my role the power to select one of
our staff members to serve on HARB uh or
the historical commission. So it does
saves a bureaucratic step uh for city
council. If you have any questions I'm
happy to answer them. Great. I have none
at the moment. Are there questions from
the
committee? Council, question from
council.
In regards
to a candidate, do you have somebody
already in mind?
Uh, in in addition to Mr. Lefver, we
actually have um a few other um of our
staff members who have the proper
certifications to serve on and the
historical commission. Uh so that would
be um at this time uh Mr. Dave Ham uh as
another person who has the uh
appropriate uh certifications. Uh there
are a couple others as well. He's sort
of the next in line in terms of
seniority, but we'll have to make a
determination based on um workload and
that type of thing. Thank you. That's
all I have. Thanks. Thank you, Councelor
Craig. Uh, Director Del, just to put a
kind of a fine point on this. Yes. I
think for me the most important um part
of these definition changes is that it
doesn't change the qualifications for
this person. It changes the number of
people that we can select um that you
can appoint uh to serve those roles. Uh
is that correct? Am I characterizing
that uh correctly? Uh that is correct
and and actually it it clarifies the
certifications that are required as well
which was not included in the old
definition. So the definition right now
doesn't have as uh many qualifications
actually listed uh and defined as the
new definition would. Uh that that is
correct. And we also discovered that
there was an opportunity to uh make sure
that it was in line with um the state
act uh governing uh historic districts
as well. And this makes no changes to
the folks that we would appoint as
members of the public to these boards,
commissions or authorities. It does not.
Thank you.
So, um, Director Gelf, what are the
qualifications?
So, um, if you look at the Department of
Labor website, there's a whole set of uh
different types of certifications for a
building uh code official. uh
certification number 15 refers to a
commercial code inspector level and
that's essentially the standard that we
would be uh upholding. There are other
certifications related to uh plumbing,
electrical um there's over um I think
there's somewhere in the range of a
dozen to 20 certifications that a
building code inspector can earn. And I
think I may have shared this with you uh
last year during the budget uh
presentation. We uh have a few master
code professionals uh in our in our
department and there's only um a small
number in the whole country. So we
really have uh a well well regarded uh
and well certified staff. Excellent. Um
are there any further questions from
council as a whole?
Are there any questions from the public?
Um, I just have a question. The historic
society is uh are you a member of the
historic
society or the historic committee?
Uh, no I'm not. And there are uh
specific um eligibility criteria for
serving on the historical commission and
the HARB. And I c I cannot serve on
either one of
those. Okay. And you're asking for a
building inspector position that will um
be a part of another
um debt on top of taxpayer dollar. So my
question is the president of the
historic society or the current building
inspector, are you saying that he's
incapable of performing these duties or
meeting these expectations and that's
why you're opening up another area to
oversee his current work? Is that what
you're implying? Miss Gomez, can I may I
endeavor to answer that question? So
this bill does not create any new
positions in the city of Lancaster. It
does not create uh any additional
employees. It does not create any
additional um employees that work on
boards, commissions, authorities. It
simply means that the the professionals
that we already have working within our
uh building codes departments can serve
on boards, commissions, and authorities.
Um expanding the definition to include
more than just one person because we
already employ more than one qualified
person. But is there currently more than
one building inspector?
Yes. And he is given full authority to
meet these criterias. He's asking for
permission to make these decisions. He's
also the bill is changing the definition
and allowing for the appointment
directly by the director of community
planning to the board's commission's
authorities, not to make anyone else a
building inspector. I'm not saying that
it's not to make anyone else. It's
giving him the authority to do somebody
else's job. No, that's not correct. So,
he's changing the definition so that he
can have an open uh he's not make this
does not allow anybody else to do
anybody else's job.
Okay. So, when he mentioned a director
of building inspector, director of
community planning to delegate that, can
you elaborate that? to delegate the
appointment to boards, commissions, and
authorities. So that's not just one city
employee, city representative who can
serve on all of them, but multiple of
those employees can serve
burden the tax. There's uh director
delves, do the city employees who are
already employed and paid by the city of
Lancaster receive any additional
compensation for serving on boards,
commissions, or authorities? They do
not. Thank you. And and just to be clear
too, the law already requires that a
building inspector sit on the uh harb
and on the historical commission. Thank
you. And is doing so currently. Correct.
Thank you.
Jose Rivera 100 block of court now.
Will you have decisions in
making what if these historical
buildings stay up or they come down?
Just just for instance, I mean I got
what three minutes just like they're
doing on uh what's that up here? Prince
Street or Prince Street where they knock
the whole building out and they just the
face of that's what you want to do.
Mr. Vera th this because that was a that
was a historical building. So they
knocked the whole building out and just
left the front of
it. That's historical. But the rest of
the building is
gone. That's what I'm asking. So this
bill has nothing to do with specific or
general decisions. You guys been
destroying the history of this city for
the longest. We have a historical
committee and it's mindless because you
guys still go and take down historical
buildings. So stop it just like the one
I'm talking about. You kept just the
face of it but and then you destroyed
the whole entire back.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
If there's no further questions, I'll
make a motion to move this to full
council on
the 13th. Second. All those in favor? I.
Thank you. That completes community
planning. Council president. Thank you,
Council Craig. We'll now move to
committee of the whole. We have a few
items under that. The first one is
council resolution number 33. This is
recognizing National Bike Month and
being introduced by councelor Hirs.
Thank you, council president. Um yeah,
bike month May uh is bike month uh
nationally and um the city has a lot of
really exciting events going on. Um I
think every time I talk about bike month
up here, I'd be remissed if I didn't
mention bikelancaster.com
uh-month. Uh if you go there, you'll see
all of the events that are coming up.
Um, I'll have more to say uh at the
third well at the, you know, assuming
this moves forward uh at the next
meeting. Um, but yeah, I think it's
really important that we've continued to
recognize um what Lancaster City could
be um as far as a safe environment for
people to bike um throughout.
So, that's all I have to say. Are there
um Well, thank you. I'm going to return
it to you. Thank you very much,
councelor Hirs. Any additional council
comments on resolution 33 at this time.
All right. From the public,
Jose Rivera, 100 block of Coral Street.
Uh me and you are a compulsive uh bike
riders, a we um and the bike lanes are
perfect. I love them. But there's one
problem.
We got company trucks parking on our
designated bike lane, especially I have
pictures. I have to develop them so you
guys could see UGI PPNL. I even seen uh
water and sewage. I seen city's halls
truck on it blocking our
road. Now the problem here is if they
blocking the bike lane on the other on
the outside
of of the street where the passenger
gets out. If they blocking that lane,
you have to go around and right now
you're jumping into
traffic. Very dangerous. I already got
pushed off the road four times. I've
seen multiple people get hurt because
the drivers do not pay attention or they
really don't care.
plain and simple. And and we all take
both the adults, we all take those bike
lanes. They're very good. They're
quick.
But we need a parking authority to start
giving tickets if they're going to park
on
that. If they want to make more money,
give them parking tickets for being on
the bike lane.
Thank you very much.
Um, I do want to respond to that because
all I will say is I I see it too. I I
hear you. Um, I see, you know,
obstructions in bike lanes. You can call
the police non-emergency line and they
will ticket those vehicles. Um, I've
I've witnessed it myself. Um, so I just
want to remind you that that is an
option. You can call the non-emergency
line. Um, and the only other thing I'll
say is like, you know, I hope that some
of these bike lanes, you know, they've
been put in in the last five five-ish
years. Um, you know, I think about what
will the culture around them be like 10,
20, 50 years from now. And I do hope
that to some extent,
um, like people, I guess, adapt to them
being there, I guess. Like I think some
of it is just the newness of them to
some extent, too. Um, yeah, that's what
I would say about that. Thank you very
much, councelor Hirs.
All right. Um, I will make a motion to
move resolution number 33 to our next
meeting on May 13th. Second. Second. All
those in favor? I I.
Our next item on the committee, the
whole is resolution number 34, 2025.
This is recognizing Asian-American,
Native, Hawaiian, and Pacific Islander
Heritage Month. I'm proud again to
introduce this resolution this year
recognizing our Asian-American, Native
Hawaiian, and Pacific Islander Heritage
uh month in Lancaster and the
contributions great and small, seen and
unseen, of the AAPI community. Um, I'd
like to thank Lancaster AAPI for their
efforts and support and uplift the
Lancaster AAPI community during this
month and all throughout the year and
events like Lunar New Year celebration
at U Plaza, which is a personal favorite
of mine. Uh they're also helping to make
some updates to this resolution that
council will will receive soon. Um and I
have invited them to attend our next
meeting on May 13th and there will be
some speakers here at that date. Um any
additional council comments on the
resolution from the
public hearing? None. I'll make a motion
to move resolution 34 forward to our
meeting on May 13th. Second. All in
favor? I thank you. The last item on the
committee of the whole agenda was to be
ethics commission applicant interviews
and I just have a brief update on those.
As you can imagine, um having folks in
uh for interviews and getting them
scheduled can be a little challenging.
Uh so we are going to be pushing them
forward to um the June 2nd committee
meeting and potentially the May 27th uh
meeting of council um depending on who
is available on what date. So, um, there
will be more information on that, uh,
moving forward. And I appreciate
council's patience as we organize those
things and appreciate your understanding
that these these things can be a little
complicated and tricky. So, we won't be
taking them up this
evening. Right. Having reached the end
of our committee meet our committee
agenda, I'll just verify uh, Mr. Harris,
the clerk's report you've sent in
writing to all members of council. Is
that right? Yes, I have. Thank you very
much. Then having reached the end of our
agenda, I'll hear a motion to adjurnn.
Motion to adjurnn. Second. All in favor?